
var questionList = [
	{question:'absorb', answer:'ซึมซับ'},
	{question:'abuse', answer:'การละเมิด'},
	{question:'adjacent', answer:'ติดกัน'},
	{question:'adjustment', answer:'การปรับ'},
	{question:'admiring', answer:'ที่เลื่อมใส'},
	{question:'admixture', answer:'ส่วนผสม'},
	{question:'adulteretion', answer:'การเจือปน'},
	{question:'aerosol', answer:'ละอองในอากาศ'},
	{question:'aggravate', answer:'ซ้ำเติม'},
	{question:'aggressive', answer:'ก้าวร้าว'},
	{question:'allusion', answer:'การพาดพิง'},
	{question:'ambitious', answer:'ทะเยอทะยาน'},
	{question:'amend', answer:'แก้ไข'},
	{question:'analyze', answer:'วิเคราะห์'},
	{question:'announce', answer:'ประกาศ'},
	{question:'anthropogenic', answer:'กิจกรรมของมนุษย์'},
	{question:'anticipating', answer:'ที่คาดการณ์ไว้'}
];
